&where2Go=Default.asp&
&introTxt=The purpose of this training is to give you the information you need to sell more Fluke test instruments to your customers. You are not expected to become a test instrument expert after this training, but you will have the tools to help your customers select the right test instrument.
&sc2Txt=This training will include several sections, including a brief overview, and sections on how to identify test tool customers, how to use the Fluke quick reference guides, how to use the Fluke ScopeMeter quick reference guide, and where to get more information. After each section, there will be a few questions to answer.
&sc3aTxt=What is a digital multimeter? That’s DMM for short.  A DMM is simply an electronic ruler for making electrical measurements. It may have any number of special features, but mainly a DMM measures volts, ohms and amps. Volts are the electrical pressure in a circuit. Ohms are the resistance in a circuit, and amps are the actual flow of current in a circuit.When a customer buys a DMM, they pick the one that has the right features, functions and price to meet their needs.
&sc3bTxt=What is a clamp meter? Sometimes your customer may need to make current measurements that exceed the built-in capabilities of their DMM. A clamp meter clamps around a single conductor to measure current without actually making contact with the metal conductor. Clamp meters measure up to 1000 amps, compared to a maximum of 10 or 20 amps for a DMM. Some clamp meters have many of the same functions as a DMM.Current clamp accessories are also available to plug into DMMs, extending the range of current they will measure.
&sc3cTxt=What is a ScopeMeter? A DMM gives information by the digits on its display that may indicate that a problem may exist. Sometimes, a technician needs more than digits to tell exactly what the problem is. After they discover the existence of a problem with their DMM, a technician may use a ScopeMeter to learn more. 

A picture is worth a thousand words, and a ScopeMeter gives a of the picture problem so it is easier to solve. The display on a ScopeMeter shows the waveform of the electrical signal so the technician can troubleshoot the problem more accurately.
&sc4Txt=Why sell test instruments? Test instruments are a good way to increase the average purchase when a customer buys components that may need to be tested.Also, when customers buy test instruments, it is a signal that they may need related products to fix the problem they are testing with the instruments. For example, if a technician buys a current clamp meter to test electric motors, it may be a good opportunity to sell that customer motors, motor drives, cable, terminators, electrical enclosures and other related products.

Compared to price-competitive, commodity products, test instruments provide a healthy profit margin to distributors.
&sc5Txt=Please select the test tool customer sales guide that best fits the type of distributor you work for. If more than one of these sales guides would be helpful, you will get a chance to go back and select another after you have reviewed the first one.
&sc5Txt2=When you are done reviewing the sales guides, click next to continue with the rest of the sales training course.
&sc5aTxt=For this section, please look at the Industrial Customer Test Tool Sales Guide.This sales tool is designed to help you identify test instrument customers at the locations you already sell to.  For various types of locations, this sales guide tells who uses test instruments and which kind of test instruments they use.  For example, if you sell to hospitals, this sales guide tells you that the facilities maintenance technicians use multimeters, clamp meters, electrical testers, and so forth. The other products they may purchase from the distributor include hand tools, power tools, air filters, lighting fixtures, fuses, safety and security equipment, outdoor equipment, pumps, plumbing and more. You can see that these test instrument users can be very profitable customers for distributors.
&sc5bTxt=For this section, please look at the Customer Test Tool Sales Guide.This sales tool is designed to help you identify test instrument customers at the locations you already sell to.  For various types of locations, this sales guide tells who uses test instruments and which kind of test instruments they use.  For example, if you sell to commercial electrical contractors, this sales guide tells you that commercial electricians use multimeters, clamp meters, electrical testers, and so forth.
&sc5cTxt=This sales tool is designed to help you identify test instrument customers at the locations you already sell to. For various types of locations, this sales guide tells who uses test instruments and which kind of test instruments they use.  For example, if you sell to communications manufacturers, bench service technicians use digital multimeters, ScopeMeters, and thermometers. The other products they may purchase from the distributor include components, soldering supplies, hand tools and static protection equipment. You can see that these test tool users can be very profitable customers for distributors.&sc7Txt=If your customer is looking for a Fluke product use the Fluke Quick Reference Guide. Please have your Fluke Quick Reference Guide handy for this section of the training.In addition to information on DMMs and clamp meters, the Fluke Quick Reference Guide contains information on a number of other types of test instruments.This guide is easy to use.  For product families that have several models, the information that is in common from one model to the next is at the top of the list of bullet points. The features of the next model higher that are different are at the bottom of the list of bullet points, printed in bold text.Let your customers read this guide to select the test instrument that best fits their needs.
&sc9Txt=If your customer is interested in a Fluke ScopeMeter, use the Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide. Please have this guide handy for this section of the training.ScopeMeters are more technically complicated than DMMs or clamp meters. The good news for you, the distributor sales associate, is that a customer who needs a ScopeMeter knows what he wants, and will be able to select one for himself using the ScopeMeter Selection Guide. You don’t need to be a ScopeMeter expert to sell them; let your customer sell himself.There are three product families of Fluke ScopeMeters. The 190B Series features a monochrome display and the 190C Series features a color display. These are the top of the line, and are used in industrial plant, manufacturing and production maintenance, as well as for electronic field service.  The ScopeMeter 120 Series, with monochrome displays, is used for industrial electrical and utility maintenance.The three main features or functions that your customer will use to choose the right ScopeMeter to meet his needs are bandwidth, sample rate, and display.Your customer will pick a Fluke ScopeMeter with only as much bandwidth as they need, so they get the performance they need at a price they want to pay. Bandwidth is the maximum frequency of a signal that can be faithfully reproduced. The more expensive Fluke ScopeMeters have more bandwidth, which is measured in megahertz. A megahertz is a million cycles per second. The range is from 20 megahertz at the low end in the Fluke ScopeMeter 123, to 200 megahertz at the high end in the Fluke 199C.Sample rate is how often the ScopeMeter takes a measurement. The more frequent the sample rate, the better the picture of the problem. The more expensive ScopeMeters have a faster sample rate.Customers that want the best picture of the problem will choose a color display. Different lines on the display appear in different colors, so it’s easier to see what‘s going on.
&sc10txt=You’re never alone out there. When you need more information than you will find on the sales tools provided in this training program, please refer to the contact information card. Please have your contact information card available for this part of the training program.For general product information and technical support, you or your customers may call 1-800-44-Fluke.The Fluke web site, at www.fluke.com, and is a great place to go for detailed product specifications and application notes.The Fluke Territory Sales Manager in your area will be glad to answer your questions and help you close sales to key accounts. For the audix phone number of your local Fluke Territory Sales Manager, look in your vendor phone list.The 1-800-FLUKE FAX system lets you send faxes of product data sheets and application notes directly to your customer by simply keying in their fax number and the document number you want to send. To get a menu of all of the documents on the system, call 1-800-FLUKE-FAX and select document number 1000.The Fluke Partner Portal is a web site designed specifically for Fluke distributors, and contains a wealth of information to help you sell more Fluke test instruments, such as product data sheets, application notes, sales guides and images. Follow the instructions on the contact information card to register for the Fluke Partner Portal. The Partner Portal allows you to down load or print files, or e-mail them to yourself so you can forward them to your customers.To order Fluke literature, please refer to the contact information card for phone and fax numbers, and an e-mail address. It helps to refer to the literature item number, which is printed in small type on the lower right hand corner of the back page of the literature item.For parts, repair and calibration, refer to the phone number on the contact information card.
&introHeader=Introduction
&sc2Header=Training Overview
&sc3aHeader=What is a digital multimeter?
&sc3bHeader=What is a clamp meter?
&sc3cHeader=What is a ScopeMeter?
&sc4Header=Why sell test instruments?
&sc5Header=Identify the Customer
&sc5aHeader=Industrial Customer Test Tool Sales Guide
&sc5bHeader=Customer Test Tool Sales Guide
&sc5cHeader=Electronic Customer Test Tool Sales Guide
&sc6Header=Better and best. Two ways to test.
&sc7Header=Fluke Quick Reference Guide
&sc9Header=Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide
&sc10Header=Where to get more information
&quiz1Desc=Industrial Customer Sales Guide
&quiz2Desc=Customer Sales Guide
&quiz3Desc=Electronic Customer Sales Guide
&quiz4Desc=Better and Best
&quiz5Desc=Fluke Quick Reference Guide
&quiz7Desc=Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide
&quiz8Desc=Contact Information Card
&retry=Retry
&good=Good
&quiz1Header=Please refer to the industrial customer test tool sales guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz1a=1. A thermometer and electrical tester are the primary tools used in a hospital by a food service worker.
&quiz1b=2. At a transportation fleet maintenance facility, an automotive mechanic would be a prime candidate for a MegOhmMeter.
&quiz1c=3. An electrician who is purchasing some motors and lighting fixtures may also need a multimeter or clamp meter, along with other tools and equipment.
&quiz2Header=Please refer to the Customer Test Tool Sales Guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz2a=1. The test tool used by a residential electrician include electrical testers, digital multimeters, clamp meters and MegOhmMeters.
&quiz2b=2. A voice, data and video cable installer would mainly use ScopeMeters.
&quiz3Header=Please refer to the electronic customer test tool sales guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz3a=1. At a communications equipment manufacturer, a research engineer would use digital multimeters, ScopeMeters and thermometers.
&quiz3b=2. At a commercial electronic system manufacturer, a production test technician would use power quality analyzers.
&quiz3c=3. A field service technician at a military base would also purchase components, soldering supplies and hand tools.
&quiz5Header=Please refer to the Fluke Quick Reference Guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz5a=1. The Fluke 179 DMM has a backlight and temperature measurement functions built-in.
&quiz5b=2. A customer needs a current measurement accessory for his DMM capable of 525 amps ac and 600 amps dc. You should recommend the Fluke i410.
&quiz5c=3. The 80TK Thermocouple Module converts any DMM into a thermometer via standard banana plugs.
&quiz5d=4. The 80PK-2A Immersion Temperature Probe is designed primarily for flat surfaces.
&quiz7Header=Please refer to the Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz7a=1. Your customer is looking for a ScopeMeter with a bandwidth of 200 megahertz, with a color display. You should recommend the Fluke 199C ScopeMeter.
&quiz7b=2. The Fluke 123 has a sample rate of 25 MS/s.
&quiz7c=3. Your customer does electronic field service for communications, radio and TV facilities.  He needs to troubleshoot and analyze complex waveforms and electronic circuits and components. You should recommend the Fluke ScopeMeter 199C.
&quiz8Header=Please refer to the Test Instrument Contact Card for the answers to these questions.
&quiz8a=1. If you need general product information or technical support on Fluke equipment, call 1-800-44-FLUKE.
&quiz8c=2. You can order literature by calling 1-800-44-FLUKE.
&evalHeader=Test Instrument Training Evaluation
&indCSG=Industrial Customer Sales Guide
&electrclCSG=Customer Test Tools Sales Guide
&electrncCSG=Electronic Customer Sales Guide
&179demo=Click here for a virtual demonstration of the Fluke 179 Digital Multimeter.
&179demoLink=about:blank
&indCSG=Industrial Customer Sales Guide
&electrclCSG=Electrical Customer Sales Guide
&electrncCSG=Electronic Customer Sales Guide
&footer1=Completed training modules are grayed-out.
&threeMainFea=3 Main Features
&bandwidth=Bandwidth
&sampleRate=Sample rate
&display=Display
&bandwidthDef=Bandwidth is the maximum frequency of a signal that can be faithfully reproduced
&sampleRateDef=Sample rate is how often the ScopeMeter takes a measurement
&notAlone=You’re never alone out there.
&varsLoaded=5&