&where2Go=Default.asp&
&introTxt=The purpose of this training is to give you the information you need to sell more Fluke and Meterman test instruments to your customers. You are not expected to become a test instrument expert after this training, but you will have the tools to help your customers select the right test instrument.
&sc2Txt=This training will include several sections, including a brief overview, and sections on how to identify test tool customers, how to help customers select the right brand of test tools, how to use the Fluke and Meterman quick reference guides, how to use the Fluke ScopeMeter quick reference guide, and where to get more information. After each section, there will be a few questions to answer.
&sc3aTxt=What is a digital multimeter? That’s DMM for short.  A DMM is simply an electronic ruler for making electrical measurements. It may have any number of special features, but mainly a DMM measures volts, ohms and amps. Volts are the electrical pressure in a circuit. Ohms are the resistance in a circuit, and amps are the actual flow of current in a circuit.When a customer buys a DMM, they pick the one that has the right features, functions and price to meet their needs.
&sc3bTxt=What is a clamp meter? Sometimes your customer may need to make current measurements that exceed the built-in capabilities of their DMM. A clamp meter clamps around a single conductor to measure current without actually making contact with the metal conductor. Clamp meters measure up to 1000 amps, compared to a maximum of 10 or 20 amps for a DMM. Some clamp meters have many of the same functions as a DMM.Current clamp accessories are also available to plug into DMMs, extending the range of current they will measure.
&sc3cTxt=What is a ScopeMeter? A DMM gives information by the digits on its display that may indicate that a problem may exist. Sometimes, a technician needs more than digits to tell exactly what the problem is. After they discover the existence of a problem with their DMM, a technician may use a ScopeMeter to learn more. 

A picture is worth a thousand words, and a ScopeMeter gives a of the picture problem so it is easier to solve. The display on a ScopeMeter shows the waveform of the electrical signal so the technician can troubleshoot the problem more accurately.
&sc4Txt=Why sell test instruments? Test instruments are a good way to increase the average purchase when a customer buys components that may need to be tested.Also, when customers buy test instruments, it is a signal that they may need related products to fix the problem they are testing with the instruments. For example, if a technician buys a current clamp meter to test electric motors, it may be a good opportunity to sell that customer motors, motor drives, cable, terminators, electrical enclosures and other related products.

Compared to price-competitive, commodity products, test instruments provide a healthy profit margin to distributors.
&sc5Txt=Please select the test tool customer sales guide that best fits the type of distributor you work for. If more than one of these sales guides would be helpful, you will get a chance to go back and select another after you have reviewed the first one.
&sc5Txt2=When you are done reviewing the sales guides, click next to continue with the rest of the sales training course.
&sc5aTxt=For this section, please look at the Industrial Customer Test Tool Sales Guide.This sales tool is designed to help you identify test instrument customers at the locations you already sell to.  For various types of locations, this sales guide tells who uses test instruments and which kind of test instruments they use.  For example, if you sell to hospitals, this sales guide tells you that the facilities maintenance technicians use multimeters, clamp meters, electrical testers, and so forth. The other products they may purchase from the distributor include hand tools, power tools, air filters, lighting fixtures, fuses, safety and security equipment, outdoor equipment, pumps, plumbing and more. You can see that these test instrument users can be very profitable customers for distributors.
&sc5bTxt=For this section, please look at the Electrical Customer Test Tool Sales Guide.This sales tool is designed to help you identify test instrument customers at the locations you already sell to.  For various types of locations, this sales guide tells who uses test instruments and which kind of test instruments they use.  For example, if you sell to commercial electrical contractors, this sales guide tells you that commercial electricians use multimeters, clamp meters, electrical testers, and so forth. The other products they may purchase from the distributor include lighting fixtures, electrical distribution equipment, motors, hand tools and more. You can see that these test instrument users can be very profitable customers for distributors.
&sc5cTxt=This sales tool is designed to help you identify test instrument customers at the locations you already sell to. For various types of locations, this sales guide tells who uses test instruments and which kind of test instruments they use.  For example, if you sell to communications manufacturers, bench service technicians use digital multimeters, ScopeMeters, and thermometers. The other products they may purchase from the distributor include components, soldering supplies, hand tools and static protection equipment. You can see that these test tool users can be very profitable customers for distributors.&sc6Txt=Please refer to the Fluke/Meterman Brand Selection Guide for this section of the training program.Fluke offers a top brand portfolio of test instruments, featuring Fluke as the “best”, or premium brand, and Meterman as the “better” or value-priced brand. This gives you a very simple, compelling “better and best” story to tell your customers, and makes it easier for your customers to pick the right brand of test instruments.So, to which customers do you sell Fluke, the “best” brand?  When the cost of down time at a facility is very high, customers will want the accuracy of a Fluke meter to help keep their world up and running.  If a technician is tough on their tools and works in a harsh environment, they demand the ruggedness and reliability of a Fluke meter.  Some customers have a desire to buy the best. You know these types; when they buy a fishing rod, they get the top-of-the-line graphite rod. When they buy a test instrument, they buy a Fluke meter. They will pay for top quality.When do you sell Meterman, the “better” brand?Some customers take a practical approach to their purchases. This is the guy that buys an economy car, even when he can afford something fancier. If your customer wants dependable quality and lots of features for the price, Meterman is their brand.  Top professionals may want a Meterman meter as a back up when their Fluke meter is not available. A foreman may get a Fluke meter, and provide Meterman meters to his crew. Meterman test instruments are supplied to distributors by Fluke Corporation, and are positioned to be its value-priced brand. With expertise from Fluke, Meterman test instruments are designed to be safer and higher quality than other brands of value-priced test instruments.The Fluke/Meterman brand selection guide will help your customer choose the right brand to meet their needs.The front of this guide tells the “better and best, two ways to test” story, and explains the benefits of the Fluke and Meterman brands.On the back of the brand selection guide, there is a multimeter selection guide and a clamp meter selection guide. The columns across the top of these guides answer the basic questions that a customer will have about which meter to buy.&sc7Txt=If your customer is looking for a Fluke product, and needs more information than found in the Fluke/Meterman Brand Selection Guide, use the Fluke Quick Reference Guide. Please have your Fluke Quick Reference Guide handy for this section of the training.In addition to information on DMMs and clamp meters, the Fluke Quick Reference Guide contains information on a number of other types of test instruments.This guide is easy to use.  For product families that have several models, the information that is in common from one model to the next is at the top of the list of bullet points. The features of the next model higher that are different are at the bottom of the list of bullet points, printed in bold text.Let your customers read this guide to select the test instrument that best fits their needs.
&sc8Txt=If your customer is looking for a Meterman test instrument, and needs more information than is found in the Fluke/Meterman Brand Selection Guide, use the Meterman Quick Reference Guide.  This guide has information on the most popular models of Meterman DMMs and clamp meters.
&sc9Txt=If your customer is interested in a Fluke ScopeMeter, use the Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide. Please have this guide handy for this section of the training.ScopeMeters are more technically complicated than DMMs or clamp meters. The good news for you, the distributor sales associate, is that a customer who needs a ScopeMeter knows what he wants, and will be able to select one for himself using the ScopeMeter Selection Guide. You don’t need to be a ScopeMeter expert to sell them; let your customer sell himself.There are three product families of Fluke ScopeMeters. The 190B Series features a monochrome display and the 190C Series features a color display. These are the top of the line, and are used in industrial plant, manufacturing and production maintenance, as well as for electronic field service.  The ScopeMeter 120 Series, with monochrome displays, is used for industrial electrical and utility maintenance.The three main features or functions that your customer will use to choose the right ScopeMeter to meet his needs are bandwidth, sample rate, and display.Your customer will pick a Fluke ScopeMeter with only as much bandwidth as they need, so they get the performance they need at a price they want to pay. Bandwidth is the maximum frequency of a signal that can be faithfully reproduced. The more expensive Fluke ScopeMeters have more bandwidth, which is measured in megahertz. A megahertz is a million cycles per second. The range is from 20 megahertz at the low end in the Fluke ScopeMeter 123, to 200 megahertz at the high end in the Fluke 199C.Sample rate is how often the ScopeMeter takes a measurement. The more frequent the sample rate, the better the picture of the problem. The more expensive ScopeMeters have a faster sample rate.Customers that want the best picture of the problem will choose a color display. Different lines on the display appear in different colors, so it’s easier to see what‘s going on.
&sc10txt=You’re never alone out there. When you need more information than you will find on the sales tools provided in this training program you can always contact your local Fluke representative.

For general product information and technical support, you or your customers may call +1.425.446.5116, or visit the Fluke web site at www.fluke.com. The web site is always a great place to go for detailed product specifications and application notes. You can also find your local Fluke representative by visiting our “Where to buy” section.Your local Fluke representative would be happy to assist you in obtaining product literature, setting up in-house seminars for you or your customers and working with you on updating the merchandising in your shop.
&introHeader=Introduction
&sc2Header=Training Overview
&sc3aHeader=What is a digital multimeter?
&sc3bHeader=What is a clamp meter?
&sc3cHeader=What is a ScopeMeter?
&sc4Header=Why sell test instruments?
&sc5Header=Identify the Customer
&sc5aHeader=Industrial Customer Test Tool Sales Guide
&sc5bHeader=Electrical Customer Test Tool Sales Guide
&sc5cHeader=Electronic Customer Test Tool Sales Guide
&sc6Header=Better and best.  Two ways to test.
&sc7Header=Fluke Quick Reference Guide
&sc8Header=Meterman Quick Reference Guide
&sc9Header=Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide
&sc10Header=Where to get more information
&quiz1Desc=Industrial Customer Sales Guide
&quiz2Desc=Electrical Customer Sales Guide
&quiz3Desc=Electronic Customer Sales Guide
&quiz4Desc=Better and Best
&quiz5Desc=Fluke Quick Reference Guide
&quiz6Desc=MeterMan Quick Reference Guide
&quiz7Desc=Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide
&retry=Retry
&good=Good
&quiz1Header=Please refer to the industrial customer test tool sales guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz1a=1. A thermometer and electrical tester are the primary tools used in a hospital by a food service worker.
&quiz1b=2. At a transportation fleet maintenance facility, an automotive mechanic would be a prime candidate for a MegOhmMeter.
&quiz1c=3. An electrician who is purchasing some motors and lighting fixtures may also need a multimeter or clamp meter, along with other tools and equipment.
&quiz2Header=Please refer to the electrical customer test tool sales guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz2a=1. The test tool used by a residential electrician include electrical testers, digital multimeters, clamp meters and MegOhmMeters.
&quiz2b=2. A voice, data and video cable installer would mainly use ScopeMeters.
&quiz2c=3. An electrician who is purchasing some motors and lighting fixtures may also need a multimeter or clamp meter, along with other tools and equipment.
&quiz3Header=Please refer to the electronic customer test tool sales guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz3a=1. At a communications equipment manufacturer, a research engineer would use digital multimeters, ScopeMeters and thermometers.
&quiz3b=2. At a commercial electronic system manufacturer, a production test technician would use power quality analyzers.
&quiz3c=3. A field service technician at a military base would also purchase components, soldering supplies and hand tools.
&quiz4Header=Please refer to the Fluke/Meterman Brand Selection Guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz4a=1. If your customer is looking for a meter with dependable quality at a value price, recommend the Meterman brand.
&quiz4b=2. If your customer is looking for a meter that is rugged, reliable and accurate (designed for a professional) recommend the Fluke brand.
&quiz4c=3. The Fluke 170 Series multimeters have a maximum voltage range of 1000 volts and have a lifetime warranty.
&quiz4d=4. Your customer is looking for a clamp meter with 100 ac amps and a maximum ac voltage range of 1000 volts. You should recommend the Fluke 335.
&quiz4e=5. The H5 Holster is a recommended accessory for the Fluke 337 Clamp Meter.
&quiz5Header=Please refer to the Fluke Quick Reference Guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz5a=1. The Fluke 179 DMM has a backlight and temperature measurement functions built-in.
&quiz5b=2. A customer needs a current measurement accessory for his DMM capable of 525 amps ac and 600 amps dc. You should recommend the Fluke i410.
&quiz5c=3. The 80TK Thermocouple Module converts any DMM into a thermometer via standard banana plugs.
&quiz5d=4. The 80PK-2A Immersion Temperature Probe (1T323) is designed primarily for flat surfaces.
&quiz6Header=Please refer to the Meterman Quick Reference Guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz6a=1. The Meterman 33XR Digital Multimeter measures up to 1000 volts ac or dc.
&quiz6b=2. The Meterman 37XR Digital Multimeter has built-in temperature measurement capability.
&quiz6c=3. Your customer wants a value priced meter with built-in temperature function capable of 2300 °F. You should recommend the Meterman 235.
&quiz6d=4. Meterman XR series digital multimeters come with a Magne-grip holster.
&quiz7Header=Please refer to the Fluke ScopeMeter Quick Reference Guide for the answers to these questions.
&quiz7a=1. Your customer is looking for a ScopeMeter with a bandwidth of 200 megahertz, with a color display. You should recommend the Fluke 199C ScopeMeter.
&quiz7b=2. The Fluke 123 has a sample rate of 25 MS/s.
&quiz7c=3. Your customer does electronic field service for communications, radio and TV facilities.  He needs to troubleshoot and analyze complex waveforms and electronic circuits and components. You should recommend the Fluke ScopeMeter 199C.
&evalHeader=Test Instrument Training Evaluation
&indCSG=Industrial Customer Sales Guide
&electrclCSG=Electrical Customer Sales Guide
&electrncCSG=Electronic Customer Sales Guide
&179demo=Click here for a virtual demonstration of the Fluke 179 Digital Multimeter.
&179demoLink=about:blank
&indCSG=Industrial Customer Sales Guide
&electrclCSG=Electrical Customer Sales Guide
&electrncCSG=Electronic Customer Sales Guide
&footer1=Completed training modules are grayed-out.
&threeMainFea=3 Main Features
&bandwidth=Bandwidth
&sampleRate=Sample rate
&display=Display
&bandwidthDef=Bandwidth is the maximum frequency of a signal that can be faithfully reproduced
&sampleRateDef=Sample rate is how often the ScopeMeter takes a measurement
&notAlone=You’re never alone out there.
&supportInfo=For general product information and technical support call 1.425.446.5116
&webInfo=www.fluke.com
&buffering=Buffering, please wait...
&trueTxt=True
&falseTxt=False
&nextButtonTxt=Next
&advance=Next
&buffering=buffering
&salesGuideList=Back to guide list
&where2buy=“Where to buy” section
&message1=You scored a
&message2=You need to score at least a 75 to get your FLUKE hat. Please try again.
&varsLoaded=5&